Hello! My name is Foxkeh.
“Foxkeh’s Wallpaper Creator” is a tool
that allows you to easily create your own
wallpaper on browser using my images.
Since it makes use of an advanced web-
based technology called SVG,
it allows for the personalization of
various designs just by using Firefox
without installing any plug-ins.
You can select the graphic and move it around,
change its size,
make it transparent
and even change the design
into a character you like.
The finished design can be made
into a wallpaper on your PC,
set as the standby wallpaper
on your mobile phone
or used as a Personas theme that allows you
to change the look of the Firefox web browser.
Let’s get creative and make
your own wallpaper on Firefox!